RG 113, Grand Army of the Republic, Department of Connecticut
Connecticut State Library
- Local Posts, 1862-1938; T000532
  - 60. Robert O. Tyler Post #50 (Hartford) (Box 27)
    - Dues receipt books (Box 32)
      - 1894-1896, 1 volume (Box 32)
    - Bank book, 1910-1930; 1 volume (Box 32)
    - Receipt books (Box 32)
      - 1881-1890, 1 volume (Box 32)
      - 1890-1896, 1 volume (Box 32)
      - 1896-1898, 1 volume (Box 32)
      - 1898-1900, 1 volume (Box 32)
      - 1900-1902, 1 volume (Box 32)
      - 1902-1903, 1 volume (Box 32)
      - 1904-1905, 1 volume (Box 32)
      - 1910-1912, 1 volume (Box 32)
      - 1912-1913, 1 volume (Box 32)
      - 1915-1916, 1 volume (Box 32)
      - 1916-1932, 1 volume (Box 32)
    - Receipts, 1894-1904; 3 folders (Box 32)
    - Receipts, 1886-1930; 3 folders (Box 33)
    - Checks and bank statements, 1917-1930; 6 folders (Box 33)
    - Trustees relief fund papers, circa 1910-1929; 2 envelopes (Box 33)
    - Bills, 1918-1925; 8 folders (Box 33)
    - Bills, 1926, 1930; 2 folders (Box 34)
    - Quartermaster reports, 1896-1905, 1914-1935; 3 folders (Box 34)
    - Trustees and auditors reports, 1884-1927; 1 folder (Box 34)
    - Relief Committee reports, 1910-1931; 1 folder (Box 34)
    - Adjutant reports, 1892-1895; shared folder (Box 34)
    - Obituary reports, 1890, 1913, 1927, 1929, 1932; shared folder (Box 34)
    - Memorial Day report, 1903; shared folder (Box 34)
    - Patriotic Instructor reports, 1925-1926; shared folder (Box 34)
    - Miscellaneous reports, 1898; shared folder (Box 34)
    - Miscellaneous, circa 1865-1929; 1 folder (Box 34)
    - Personal vitas, 1879-1915; 3 folders (Box 34)
    - Applications for membership, 1861-1912; 8 folders (Box 34)
      Arranged numerically by application number (1-700) plus some unnumbered applications.
    - Transfer cards, 1875-1925; 1 folder (Box 34)
  - 61. Marvin Wait Post #51 (Dayville) (Box 35)
    - Adjutant reports, 1899-1895; 1 folder (Box 35)
    - Descriptive book, 1 volume (Box 35)
    - Minute books (Box 35)
      - 1880-1891, 1 volume (Box 35)
      - 1891-1899, 1 volume (Box 35)
    - Dues book, 1880-1897; 1 volume (Box 35)
    - Receipt book, 1888-1895; 1 volume (Box 35)
    - Cash book, 1888-1894; 1 volume (Box 35)
  - 62. Henry C. Merwin Post #52 (New Haven) (Box 35)
    - Descriptive book, 2 volumes (original + photostat) (Box 35)
    - Adjutant reports, 1892-1895; 1 folder (Box 35)
  - 63. Joseph K.F. Mansfield Post #53 (Middletown) (Box 35)
    - Adjutant reports, 1892-1895; shared folder (Box 35)
    - Obituary reports, 1890; shared folder (Box 35)
    - Transfer card, 1903; shared folder (Box 35)
    - Correspondence, 1897; shared folder (Box 35)
    - Memorial book, 1 volume (Box 35A)
  - 64. Addison G. Warner Post #54 (Putnam) (Box 35)
    - Adjutant reports, 1892-1895; shared folder (Box 35)
    - Obituary reports, 1890; shared folder (Box 35)
  - 65. Williams Post #55 (Mystic) (Box 35)
    - Adjutant reports, 1893-1895; shared folder (Box 35)
    - Obituary reports, 1890; shared folder (Box 35)
  - 66. Samuel Brown Post #56 (Thompsonville) (Box 35)
    - Adjutant reports, 1892-1895; shared folder (Box 35)
    - Correspondence, 1914; shared folder (Box 35)
    - Descriptive book, 1 volume (Box 35)
    - Memorial book, 1904; 1 volume (Box 35)
    - Roll book, 1 volume (Box 35)
    - Minute book, 1915-1928; 1 volume (Box 35)
      Includes newspaper clippings.
    - Ledger book, 1882-1891; 1 volume (Box 35)
  - 67. Newton S. Manross Post #57 (Forestville) (Box 35)
    - Adjutant reports, 1892-1895; 1 folder (Box 35)
  - 68. O.H. Knight Post #58 (Lakeville) (Box 35)
    - Adjutant reports, 1892-1895; 1 folder (Box 35)
  - 69. John M. Gregory Post #59 (Sharon) (Box 35)
    - Adjutant reports, 1892-1894; shared folder (Box 35)
    - Obituary reports, 1890; shared folder (Box 35)
  - 70. David S. Cowles Post #60 (Canaan) (Box 36)
    - Adjutant reports, 1892-1895; 1 folder (Box 36)
    - Descriptive book, 1 volume (Box 36)
    - Dues book, 1882-1924; 1 volume (Box 36)
    - Cash book, 1882-1923; 1 volume (Box 36)
    - Minute books (Box 36)
      - 1882-1904, 1 volume (Box 36)
      - 1905-1924, 1 volume (Box 36)
    - Rules and regulations and by-laws, 1 volume (Box 36)
      Includes inventory, 1924.
  - 71. Samuel P. Ferris Post #61 (New Canaan) (Box 36)
    - Adjutant reports, 1892-1894; shared folder (Box 36)
    - Obituary reports, 1890; shared folder (Box 36)
    - Descriptive book, 1 volume (Box 36)
  - 72. Ambrose E. Burnside Post #62 (Unionville) (Box 36)
    - Adjutant reports, 1892-1894; shared folder (Box 36)
    - Obituary reports, 1890; shared folder (Box 36)
    - Miscellaneous papers, 1896-1923; shared folder (Box 36)
    - Descriptive book, 1 volume (Box 36)
    - Receipt book, 1896-1909; 1 volume (Box 36)
    - Cash book, 1890-1912; 1 volume (Box 36)
    - Bible, 1888; 1 volume (Box 36)
  - 73. Harry McDonough Post #63 (Westport) (Box 37)
    - Adjutant reports, 1892-1895; 1 folder (Box 37)
    - Minute book, 1888-1904; 1 volume (Box 37)
    - Dues account book, 1894-1904; 1 volume (Box 37)
    - Cash book, 1894-1905; 1 volume (Box 37)
  - 74. Edwin D. Pickett Post #64 (Ridgefield) (Box 37)
    - Adjutant reports, 1892-1894; shared folder (Box 37)
    - Obituary reports, 1890; shared folder (Box 37)
    - Descriptive book, 1 volume (Box 37)
    - Medical descriptive book, 1 volume (Box 37)
    - Minute book, 1893-1895; 1 volume (Box 37)
    - Roll book, 1 volume (Box 37)
    - Quartermaster record book, 1883-1888; 1 volume (Box 37)
  - 75. Daniel C. Rodman Post #65 (East Hartford) (Box 37)
    - Adjutant reports, 1892-1894; shared folder (Box 37)
    - Obituary reports, 1890; shared folder (Box 37)
  - 76. John M. Morris Post #66 (Wethersfield) (Box 37)
    - Minute books (Box 37)
      - 1884-1888, 1 volume (Box 37)
      - 1888-1891, 1 volume (Box 37)
      - 1891-1896, 1 volume (Box 37)
      - 1896-1901, 1 volume (Box 37)
      - 1902-1904, 1 volume (Box 37)
      - 1904-1908, 1 volume (Box 37)
      - 1908-1912, 1 volume (Box 37)
      - 1913-1918, 1 volume (Box 37)
    - Account book, 1894-1913; 1 volume (Box 37)
      Includes dues and other accounts.
    - Descriptive book, 1 volume (Box 38)
    - By-laws, 1 volume (Box 38)
    - Membership applications, 1869-1918; 1 folder (Box 38)
    - Quartermaster reports, 1884-191; 1 folder (Box 38)
    - Receipts, 1884-1928; 1 folder (Box 38)
    - Adjutant reports and attendance, 1884-1897; 1 folder (Box 38)
    - Miscellaneous, 1883-1920, undated (Box 38)
    - Miscellaneous reports, 1 folder (Box 38)
      - Relief fund reports, 1901-1908 (Box 38)
      - Obituary reports, 1890-1891 (Box 38)
      - Adjutant and quartermaster reports, 1897-1898, 1905-1906, 1913 (Box 38)
    - Correspondence, 1894-1913; shared folder (Box 38)
  - 77. Joseph H. Converse Post #67 (Windsor Locks) (Box 39)
    - Adjutant reports, 1892-1895; shared folder (Box 39)
    - Obituary reports, 1890; shared folder (Box 39)
    - Transfer card, 1890; shared folder (Box 39)
    - Memorial Hall dedication book, 1891 (Box 39)
  - 78. Charles L. Russell Post #68 (Thomaston) (Box 39)
    - Descriptive book, negative photostat, shared folder (Box 39)
    - Adjutant reports, 1892-1895; shared folder (Box 39)
  - 79. P.M. Trowbridge Post #69 (Woodbury) (Box 39)
    - Adjutant reports, 1892-1895; 1 folder (Box 39)
    - Descriptive book, 1 volume (Box 39)
    - Dues account book, 1884-1895; 1 volume (Box 39)
    - Minute books (Box 39)
      - 1884-1886, 1 volume (Box 39)
      - 1886-1894, 1 volume (Box 39)
  - 80. Sylvester C. Bugbee Post #70 (Tolland) (Box 39)
    - Applications for membership, 1884-1889; shared folder (Box 39)
    - Adjutant reports, 1884-1895; shared folder (Box 39)
    - Quartermaster reports, 1888-1892; shared folder (Box 39)
    - Attendance reports, 1884-1895; shared folder (Box 39)
    - Miscellaneous papers, 1884-1890; shared folder (Box 39)
    - Minute book, 1884-1895; 1 volume (Box 39)
    - Dues account book, 1884-1895; 1 volume (Box 39)
  - 81. Thomas F. Burpee Post #71 (Rockville) (Box 39)
    - Adjutant reports, 1892-1895; shared folder (Box 39)
    - Obituary reports, 1890; shared folder (Box 39)
    - Attendance report, 1892; shared folder (Box 39)
  - 82. Jedediah Chapman Post #72 (Westbrook (Box 39)
    - Adjutant reports, 1892-1895; shared folder (Box 39)
    - Obituary reports, 1890; shared folder (Box 39)
    - Attendance report, undated; shared folder (Box 39)
  - 83. David P. Corbin Post #74 (Union) (Box 39)
    - Adjutant reports, 1892-1895; 1 folder (Box 39)
  - 84. T.M. Redshaw Post #75 (Ansonia) (Box 39)
    - Adjutant reports, 1892-1895; shared folder (Box 39)
    - Obituary reports, 1890; shared folder (Box 39)
    - Correspondence, 1926-1928, undated; shared folder (Box 39)
    - Minute books (Box 39)
      - 1901-1906, 1 volume (Box 39)
      - 1917-1926, 1 volume (Box 39)
    - Cash book, 1904-1927; 1 volume (Box 39)
    - Receipt book, 1916-1927; 1 volume (Box 39)
  - 85. Gen. A. Von Steinwehr Post #76 (New Haven) (Box 40)
    - Adjutant reports, 1892-1895; 1 folder (Box 40)
  - 86. James B. Kilbourn Post #77 (Central Village) (Box 40)
    - Applications for membership and transfer cards, 1868-1891, undated; 1 folder (Box 40)
    - Adjutant reports, 1892-1895; shared folder (Box 40)
    - Obituary reports, 1890; shared folder (Box 40)
    - Quartermaster reports, 1888-1890; shared folder (Box 40)
    - Adjutant and Quartermaster reports, 1903-1907; shared folder (Box 40)
    - Accounts, 1899-1909; shared folder (Box 40)
    - Receipts, 1898-1910; shared folder (Box 40)
    - Memorial Day reports, 1906, 1908; shared folder (Box 40)
    - Discharge paper, 1865; shared folder (Box 40)
    - Minute book, 1886-1897; 1 volume (Box 40)
    - Descriptive book, 1 volume (Box 40)
  - 87. Edwin R. Lee Post #78 (New Hartford) (Box 40)
    - Adjutant reports, 1892-1895; 1 folder (Box 40)
    - Descriptive book, 1 volume (Box 40)
  - 88. T.G. Brown Post #79 (Chaplin) (Box 40)
    - Applications for membership, 1886-1914, undated; shared folder (Box 40)
    - Insurance policies, 1895-1915; shared folder (Box 40)
    - Bonds, 1889, 1891; shared folder (Box 40)
    - Transfer card, 1891; shared folder (Box 40)
    - Miscellaneous papers, 1887-1914; 1 folder (Box 40)
    - Adjutant reports, obituary reports, attendance reports, Quartermaster reports, Adjutant and Quartermaster reports, 1888-1917; 1 folder (Box 40)
    - Descriptive book, 1 volume (Box 40)
    - Minute book, 1983-1924; 1 volume (Box 40, Folder 79)
    - Cash book, 1891-1920; 1 volume (Box 40)
    - Dues books (Box 40)
      - 1886-1891, 1 volume (Box 40)
      - 1889-1920, 1 volume (Box 40)
  - 89. Seth F. Plumb Post #80 (Litchfield) (Box 40)
    - Adjutant reports, 1892-1895; 1 folder (Box 40)
  - 90. Hancock Post #81 (Westerly R.I.) (Box 40)
    - Adjutant reports, 1892-1895; shared folder (Box 40)
    - Obituary reports, 1890; shared folder (Box 40)
    - Minute books (Box 40)
      - 1886-1898, 1 volume (Box 40)
      - 1898-1918, 1 volume (Box 40)
      - 1918-1921, 1 volume (Box 40)
        Includes by-laws.
    - Descriptive books, 1 volume (Box 40)
    - Dues account book, 1886-1910; 1 volume (Box 40)
  - 91. John F. Trumbull Post #82 (Stonington) (Box 41)
    - Adjutant reports, 1892-1895; 1 folder (Box 41)
    - Descriptive book, 1 volume (Box 41)
  - 92. Joseph R. Fay Post #83 (Simsbury) (Box 41)
    - Adjutant reports, 1892-1895; 1 folder (Box 41)
    - Descriptive book, 1 volume (Box 41)
    - Minute book, 1889-1905; 1 volume (Box 41)
    - Dues account book, 1889-1905; 1 volume (Box 41)
    - Cash book, 1889-1905; 1 volume (Box 41)
  - 93. Henry W. Kingsbury Post #84 (Old Lyme) (Box 41)
    - Adjutant reports, 1892-1895; shared folder (Box 41)
    - Obituary reports, 1890; shared folder (Box 41)
    - Descriptive book, 1 volume (Box 41)
    - Minute book, 1889-1898; 1 volume (Box 41)
  - 94. William T. Minor Post #85 (Stamford) (Box 41)
    - Adjutant reports, 1893-1894; 1 folder (Box 41)
    - Minute books (Box 41)
      - 1892 December 7 - 1895 August 22, 1 volume (Box 41)
      - 1895 August 29 - 1899 March 30, 1 volume (Box 41)
      - 1899 April 6 - 1903 December 31, 1 volume (Box 41)
      - 1904 January 7 - 1909 October 21, 1 volume (Box 41)
      - 1909 October 28 - 1914 September 17, 1 volume (Box 41)
      - 1914 September 24 - 1929 January 5, 1 volume (Box 41)
      - 1828 April 6 - 1933 September 21, 1 volume (Box 41)
      - 1903 January 8 - 1904 May 12, 1 notebook (Box 41)
    - Roll book, 1 volume (Box 42)
    - Registry book, 1908-1922; 1 volume (Box 42)
    - Memorial Day Committee minute book, 1908-1916; 1 volume (Box 42)
      Includes minutes, 1908-1909; contributions received, 1913-1916
  - 95. Elisha Johnson Post #86 (Willington) (Box 42)
    - Adjutant reports, 1893-1895; shared folder (Box 42)
    - Attendance report, 1895; shared folder (Box 42)
    - Resolution, 1868; shared folder (Box 42)
    - Descriptive books, 2 volumes (Box 42)
    - Roll book, 1 volume (Box 42)
    - Minute book, 1893-1899; 1 volume (Box 42)
    - Cash book, 1893-1899; 1 volume (Box 42)
    - Dues account book, 1894-1898; 1 volume (Box 42)
    - Receipt book, 1893-1898; 1 volume (Box 42)
  - 96. Nelson L. White Post #87 (Danbury) (Box 42)
    - Adjutant reports, 1893-1895; 1 folder (Box 42)
- Addenda, 1911-1935
  - Lists and Testimonies, 1929-1935; 1993-041; shared box
  - Burial Records, 1911, 1925; 2002-072; 1 volume